{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Do you read very many books? Yes, _________.",
      "a": "very little",
      "b": "quite a few",
      "c": "just a little",
      "d": "very few of them",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- quite + a few (for countable nouns)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Did you tell Ted and Mary about our change in plans? \"Yes, I told them we'd be ___.\"",
      "a": "a little late",
      "b": "a few late hours",
      "c": "late several hours",
      "d": "to some late",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- A little + adj \n- A few + n + adj",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Glad to see you again. \"Would you like ___ hot coffee?\"",
      "a": "any",
      "b": "any more",
      "c": "some",
      "d": "some any",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Would you like some ...?",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "You should be _________ towards seniors.",
      "a": "respectable",
      "b": "respectful",
      "c": "respective",
      "d": "respecting",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- To be respectful towards somebody",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "The solution of the problem is very _________ to the development of our economy.",
      "a": "momentary",
      "b": "momently",
      "c": "momentous",
      "d": "momental",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- A momentous event, change, or decision is very important because it will have a great influence on the future.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Any unilateral action is a _________ undertaking.",
      "a": "world-wide",
      "b": "cooperative",
      "c": "one-sided",
      "d": "malicious",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- One-sided (adj): Considering or showing only one side of a question, subject etc in a way that is unfair.",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "He was an ___ statesman and diplomat; his record was untarnished by scandals or rumors, and the public treated him with great respect.",
      "a": "imminent",
      "b": "eminent",
      "c": "envious",
      "d": "immediate",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- An eminent person is famous, important, and respected",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Men, since they are by nature ___, necessarily die.",
      "a": "moral",
      "b": "immoral",
      "c": "immortal",
      "d": "mortal",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Mortal = not able to live for ever (opp: immortal)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ more to be pitied than blamed.",
      "a": "The uneducated are",
      "b": "The uneducated is",
      "c": "Uneducated are",
      "d": "Uneducated is",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- The + adj (plural noun) + are",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "I hear that you're having a house built. Is it finished yet ? \"No, but it's ___ completion.\"",
      "a": "nearly to",
      "b": "almost at",
      "c": "close to",
      "d": "about at",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Be close to something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "4",
      "subcategorylv2": "2",
      "type": "5"
    }
  ]
}